(Sheldon:)Dr. Leonard Hofstadter,
(Sheldon:)you are officially charged
(Sheldon:)with two violations
of the roommate agreement.
(Sheldon:)Do you waive
(Sheldon:)reading of the charges?
(Leonard:)Yeah, fine.
(Priya:)Hang on. No.
(Priya:)My client does not waive
reading of the charges.
(Priya:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Cool. I've got
a lawyer.
(Leonard:)And I've seen her naked.
(Priya:)Proceed.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
"Count the first:
"On or about
the 28th day of April,
"the accused did knowingly
and with malice aforethought
"deny access
to the shared bathroom
"in a time of emergency, to wit,
my back teeth were floating.
"Count the second:
the accused exceeded
"the agreed upon occupancy
of the shower,
"to wit, one,
unless we are under attack
by water-soluble aliens."
(Priya:)Can I see
the roommate agreement?